qr-code-generator.com 2018-02-07

# 

We respect your private and personal sphere, because privacy is a matter of trust and trust is important to us. The protection and the collection, processing and use of your personal information in accordance with the legal requirements is an important concern to us. In order for you to feel secure when you visit our websites, we therefore strictly follow the legal regulations when processing your personal data and would like to inform you about our data collection and use of data here. You may download or save this document by using the usual functionality of your browser for printing websites. You may also download and archieve this document as a PDF by [clicking here](http://cdnqrcgde.s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Datenschutzerklaerung.pdf). To open this file use the free program Adobe Reader (at www.adobe.com) or comparable programs that run the PDF format. With the acceptance of the following Privacy Policy, you consent to the Egoditor UG (haftungsbeschränkt), Weststraße 93, 33615 Bielefeld (hereinafter referred to: Egoditor), operator of the website www.qrcode-generator.com, collecting, processing and using your personal data under observance of the data protection laws and the following provisions.

* * *

### 01\. Responsible Office and Contact

Responsible office in accordance with the German Data Protection Act, for the collection, processing and use of your personal data, is:

Egoditor UG (haftungsbeschränkt)  
Am Lenkwerk 13  
33609 Bielefeld

In case you want to disagree with the collection, processing or use of your personal data according this Privacy Policy, you can do so via email, fax or letter using the following contact data:

### 02\. Collection, Processing and Use of Personal Data

Personal data is only collected if you provide it to us by concluding a contract, creating a user account, signing up for our email newsletter or requesting offers. Personal data is data which contains information about personal and factual circumstances of a certain user. This data will be used without your express approval and only for the performance of contracts or the processing of your requests.

### 03\. Processing of Personal Data

Your personal data will not be passed on to third parties unless such passing on is not neccessary for the provision or billing of contractual services or if there is a legal disclosure obligation. An exeption exists only if the user has expressly given his consent for this, which may be revoked at any time.

### 04\. Newsletter

We use the so-called double opt in procedure for the subscription to our newsletter, i.e. after signing up to our newsletter we will send you a notification email and ask you to confirm that you would like to receive our newsletter by clicking a link. In case you do not want to receive our newsletter anymore, you may refuse to receive it at any time without incurring any costs other than the transmission costs in accordance with the basic tariffs. A written notification to the contact data mentioned in clause 1 is sufficient. In addition, you will find an unsubscribe link in every newsletter.

### 05\. Essential Information

Egoditor is entitled to contact you in case of relevant changes in the area of conditions or services that are essential for the duration of the contractual relationship via phone, email, fax or letter.

### 06\. Cookies

The website uses so-called “cookies” which serve to make the Internet presence more user-friendly, effective and safe. Furthermore, cookies allow us to measure the frequency of page views and the general navigation. Please note that some of these cookies, in most cases so-caled “session cookies”, will be transferred from our server onto your system. Session cookies delete themselves again automatically from your hard drive. Of course you may decline to accept cookies as long as your browser allows this.

### 07\. Log Files

During each access to the websites of Egoditor usage data will be transmitted by the respective Internet browser and saved in protocol files, so-called server log files. The stored data records contain the following data: date and time of access, name of the accessed site, IP address, referrer URL, the volume of data transmited as well as product and version information of the used browser. IP addresses of users will be deleted or made anonymous following termination of use. Anonymizing IP addresses means to change them so that single details about personal and factual circumstances cannot be related to a specific or identifiable natural person. These log file data records will be evaluated in an anonymized form in order to improve our services and offers and make them more user-friendly, find and correct errors and to control the utilization of servers.

### 08\. Web Analysis with Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, text files, that will be saved on your computer and allow an analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie concerning your use of this website will be generally passed on to a Google server in the USA and saved there. In case of an activation of the IP anonymization for this website, your IP address will be shortened by Google within member states of the European Union or in other Contracting States to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. The complete IP address will only be transmitted to a server of Google in the USA and shortened there in exceptional cases. On behalf of the website operator, Google will use these information in order to evaluate your website usage, create reports about website activities for the website operator and provide other services related to the use of the website and the Internet. The IP address transmitted by your browser will not be combined with other data held by Google. You may decline to accept cookies in your browser settings; however, please note that if you do so, you might not be able to make full use of all the functions on this website. You may also prevent the collection of data (including your IP address) that is related to your use of the website and generated by cookies as well as the processing of this data by Google simply by downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following website: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

### 09\. Google Ad Sense

This website uses Google AdSense, a service for integrating advertisements of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google AdSense uses so-called “Cookies”, text data that is saved on your computer and allows the analysis of the use of the website. Google AdSense also uses so-called Web beacons (invisible graphics). These Web beacons enable the analysis of information such as the traffic on these sites. Information about the use of this website (including your IP adress) and the delivery of advertising formats generated by cookies and Web beacons will be processed to a server of Google in the USA and will be saved there. This information my be processed to contractual partners of Google by Google. Google will not associate your IP adress with any other Google data. You may decline to accept cookies in your browser settings; however, please note that if you do so, you might not be able to make full use of all the functions on this website. Through the use of this website, you express your consent to the processing of data collected by Google about you in the manner described above and for the purposes previously mentioned.

### 10\. Use of Social Media Services

###### 10.1 Facebook Plugins (e.g. Like-Buttons)

Plugins of the social network facebook, 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA are integrated in our websites. Facebook plugins are indicated by the facebook logo or the “Like-button” on our website.

You will find an overview of facebook plugins at the following website:   
<http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>

When you visit our websites a direct connection between your browser and facebook’s servers will be established. Facebook then is notified of the fact that you have called up the corresponding page on our website. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking “Like” while you are logged in to facebook, you may link content of our website on your facebook profile. Thereby, facebook can relate your website visit to your user account. Please note that we, as the website provider, know nothing about the content of data processed and used by facebook.

Further information can be found in facebook’s privacy policy at the following website:  
<https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy>

If you do not wish to have data collected about you by facebook via our website, you need to log out of facebook before visiting the site.

###### 10.2 Twitter

Our websites use functions of the service twitter. These functions are provided by Twitter Inc., Twitter, Inc. 1355. Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA. If you interact with twitter and the function “Re-Tweet”, websites visited by you will be related to your twitter account and will be visible for other users. Data will also be transferred to twitter through this. Please note that we, as the website provider, know nothing about the content of data processed and used by twitter. Further information can be found in twitter’s privacy policy at the following website: <http://twitter.com/privacy>

You may change your twitter privacy settings in your account settings at: <http://twitter.com/privacy>

###### 10.3 Google +1

###### Collection and processing of information

With the Google +1 button you may publish information worldwide. In addition, you and other users receive personalized content from Google and our partners. Google saves the information that you have given +1 for a content as well as information about the site that you have visited when you have clicked on +1. Your +1 may be shown on the Internet in combination with your profile name and your picture in Google services (e.g. in search results or in your Google profile) or elsewhere on websites or advertisements. Google stores information about your +1 activities in order to improve Google services for you and others. In order to use the Google +1 button, you need a worldwide-visible, public Google profile that must at least contain the name chosen for the profile. This name is used in all Google services. In some cases this name may also replace an other name that you have used while sharing content under your Google account. The identity of your Google profile may be displayed to users who know your email address or have other personally-identifying information about you.

###### Use of collected information

With the Google +1 button you may publish information worldwide. In addition, you and other users receive personalized content from Google and our partners. Google saves the information that you have given +1 for a content as well as information about the site that you have visited when you have clicked on +1. Your +1 may be shown on the Internet in combination with your profile name and your picture in Google services (e.g. in search results or in your Google profile) or elsewhere on websites or advertisements. Google stores information about your +1 activities in order to improve Google services for you and others. In order to use the Google +1 button, you need a worldwide-visible, public Google profile that must at least contain the name chosen for the profile. This name is used in all Google services. In some cases this name may also replace an other name that you have used while sharing content under your Google account. The identity of your Google profile may be displayed to users who know your email address or have other personally-identifying information about you.

### 11\. Web Analysis with Google Analytics

This website uses Google Remarketing Tags. They are services provided by Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA; hereafter referred to as "Google"). Google uses cookies that are saved on your computer and enable the evaluation of your website usage. The information generated by the cookies (including your IP address) is transmitted to and stored by Google on a server in the United States. Google truncates the IP address by three last digits, therefore an exact identification of a user by the IP address is no longer possible.

Google complies with the privacy principles by US-EU Safe Harbour Framework and is registered in the Safe Harbour program by the US Department of Commerce. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, compiling reports for the web site owner on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google will also transfer this information to a third party, if the law requires it or if the third party processes this data under Google’s request. Third parties, including Google, run advertisements on Internet sites.Third parties, including Google, will serve advertisements based on saved cookies with information about a user’s previous visits to this website. Google will on no account combine your IP address with other data.

You may refuse data collection and storage any time, with effect for the future. You can disable the use of cookies by Google by visiting the page for [opting out of Google advertisements](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). However, please note that in this case you may be unable to use some features of this website to the full extent. Through the use of this website, you express your consent to the processing of data collected by Google about you in the manner described above and for the purpose previously mentioned.

You may refuse data collection and storage any time, with effect for the future. You can find further information on Google’s policies [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### 12\. Right of Access

You have the right to become informed gratuitously about your saved data and the right of rectification, disabling and deletion of personal data. If you have any questions concerning the collection, processing or use of your personal data, please contact us. The same is valid for information, deletion and change requests regarding your personal data as well as for revocation of given consent. The contact address can be found in our Legal Notice.
